https://colorado.sportswar.com/privacy-policy/

NetBuffs.com Login
Password:
LoginSign Up
Skip to content
Where Colorado Buffalo alumni, fans and friends come to chat all things CU.
Go Buffs!
NetBuffs.com knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting our website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy covers NetBuffs.com’s treatment of personal information that NetBuffs.com gathers when you are on the NetBuffs.com website and when you use NetBuffs.com services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that NetBuffs.com does not own or control, or to individuals that NetBuffs.com does not employ or manage.
Information Collected by NetBuffs.com
We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. We collect the following types of information from our NetBuffs.com users:
1. Information You Provide to Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features.
2. Automatic Information:
We
receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with
us. NetBuffs.com and its authorized agents automatically receive and
record certain “traffic data” on their server logs from your
browser including your IP address, NetBuffs.com cookie information, and
the page you requested. NetBuffs.com uses this traffic data to help
diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the
website.
NetBuffs.com
may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed.
Many
companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously.
While NetBuffs.com will not be able to provide you with a personalized
experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these
programs are available.
E-mail Communications
NetBuffs.com is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the “Sharing Your Information” section below. NetBuffs.com may send out e-mails with NetBuffs.com-related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions.
Cookies
Cookies
are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard
drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your
browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by
how many people. NetBuffs.com cookies do not collect personal
information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies
with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen
name or e-mail address is.
The
“help” portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will
direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how
to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how
to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies
activated because cookies allow you to use some of NetBuffs.com’s
coolest features.
NetBuffs.com’s
advertising partners may place a cookie on your browser that makes it
possible to collect anonymous non-personally identifiable information that
ad delivery systems use to present more relevant ads. If you would prefer
to opt-out of this standard practice, please visit our advertising partner
Platform-A’s privacy policy and opt-out page.
Sharing Your Information
Rest assured that we neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone and that we will share your personal information only as described below.
NetBuffs.com
Personnel: NetBuffs.com personnel and authorized consultants and/or
contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal
course of NetBuffs.com business.
Business
Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these
types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business
assets that is transferred. Moreover, if NetBuffs.com, or
substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be
one of the assets that is transferred.
Protection
of NetBuffs.com and Others: We may release personal information when
we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law;
to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the
rights, property, or safety of NetBuffs.com, our employees, our users,
or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and
organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Syndication:
NetBuffs.com allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public
content within the NetBuffs.com website.
With
Your Consent: Except as noted above, we will contact you when your
personal information is shared with third parties or used for a purpose
incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected,
and you will be able to opt out to prevent the sharing of this
information.
Advertising
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
Children Under 18 Years of Age
You must be 13 years and older to register to use the NetBuffs.com website. As a result, NetBuffs.com does not specifically collect information about children. If we learn that NetBuffs.com has collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 18 ask and receive their parents’ permission before using NetBuffs.com or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
NetBuffs.com may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the NetBuffs.com website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.
Conditions of Use
If you decide to visit NetBuffs.com website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.
Effective Date of this Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of March 1, 2011.
All Boards
What’s New? (Latest Posts)
RamNation.com (CSU)
TechSideline.com (VT)
TheSabre.com (Virginia)
DreamBackfield.com (Pitt)
DawgRun.com (Georgia)
HoopsIntel.com (recruiting)
